it is the year 1999 a TV show is
broadcasted in France and while many
will consider a simple site morning
cartoon it would change the lives of
many as if it is the second coming of
Jesus Christ so take my hand as
a walk through the wonderful history
that is sock Underground
now you gotta remember this was
the nannies this was the air were good
cartoons didn't even exist just imagine
you excitement you wake up for school
get your bowl of raisin bran or some
turn on the TV and you see Sonic
Underground set a foundation for what
cartoons
should always strive to be needless to
say this show is bitchin and if you
think otherwise well you're just wrong
to start things off I think it'd be best
if we go back to the beginning Sonic
Underground began airing in 99 odd on
the 6th of January now this was only in
France for the time being
but the rest of the world did eventually
get sucked Underground like America did
for example a few months later the show
began airing in America in August so it
was a little behind the front version
and but this didn't really bother
me because as most of you may already
know I can speak and read perfect French
so unlike most I was already caught up
with the current episodes and which
brings me to the overall plot of the
show the main focus of it all is about
the Hedgehog triplets Sonic Manic and
Sonya trying to find the mother who just
so happens to be the former queen of the
planet Mobius pretty bitchin most of the
beginning episodes I mainly to introduce
the cast and set up for the future plot
if you will and this this is where the
hits the fan I remember like
it was yesterday I was watching soccer
on beginnings that's up someone by the
way and I saw this man I couldn't
believe my eyes I was like he's so sexy
how could a man so sexy be on a kid show
and then he left I thought okay so I
guess he's just a backing character okay
then but then he appeared again then
again and and then a hit me this
guy's not back in character he's a side
character he is the best kind of Cathy
you want to see more of him but you just
can't he's not quite main character so
you don't get enough of him he it's like
a tease like and shits up when he's on
screen you want to see more of him but
you can
because he's a side character and
then this this is really when I realized
how great Sonic Underground is it's cast
of characters are so lovable so cool and
hip and I realized this is the
Sonic Underground was made by DIC
entertainment some of you may know them
because they make TV shows like the
Doodlebops
eventually Sark Underground was bought
by Cookie John entertainment another
cartoon company then yeah if you're
wondering the they bought the Doodlebops
too so yeah I know what you're thinking
wait what the so apparently this
random-ass company came along and bought
the goods DIC entertainment was going
out of business which eventually led to
cookie jail entertainment too by DIC
entertainment
although get this I you not
2012 cookie jar entertainment files for
bankruptcy and they all then bought out
by another company called dhx
media this is one of the reasons why
sock town is not on TV anymore because
at this point in time nobody is even
sure who the owns Sonic on the
ground let alone its rights to the
characters there have been rumors going
around though that Ben Hearst the
director of Sonic Underground still owns
the rights although nobody really knows
for sure
they say that the voice actors could
even make or break a TV show and I gotta
say Sonic I'm gonna is the
greatest show I've ever seen when it
comes to the voice acting the amount of
emotion they can show at times is just
breathtaking
you don't see this nowadays I think it
would be best if I show you a scene so
you can see for yourself
Sonic listen to me run as fast as you
can to Uncle Chuck don't stop and don't
look back what about you we'll be okay
Sonny but you know what I need to see
the biggest Rev you've ever done really
want me to win
sure do pal let's see as you can see
they are able to fit in many types of
emotions in that one scene alone
happiness sadness and despair this is
the matter of DT you get in every moment
of the show this is all thanks to the
wonderful cast most notably of course
julia watt who not only voice Sonic but
his siblings Matt and Sonia as well but
he didn't stop there he also was
other side characters such as Armand
Rafi other notable voice as would be Ian
James Colette as Knuckles the Echidna mu
isla mark as dr. Ivo Banach and of
course even a couple celebrities got to
ass in there like Sean Connery as Athair
I mean why the now I'm where I only
the best for Sonic Underground
now I'm sure we can all agree
sarcone is the Bobby
you're asking yourself why was it
canceled well that can be explained
everyone I don't give a it all
started Epson one or more over the first
eighteen you see since the show was just
getting started
they didn't want to focus on the plot
right away and yeah that's all fine and
bitchin but I want to see the goods so
soccer was already dropping the boss and
so you know what they did that's right
they did the obvious they
introduced the KKnux
into the show the downside to this was
well let's just let's just say the
animation isn't bitchin I mean just
Jesus Christ and to add more salt to the
wound not cuz even appear on the
official boxer as a main character even
though he was only in one shitty episode
and this my is where we enter
the Dark Age of Sonic on the ground
episodes 20 through 26
most of these episodes consisted of
nothing but filler that did not progress
the plot in any way shape or
form
episode 22 is that one with that
stupid robot baby this is widely
popularized as the worst episode in
Sonic Underground history I mean the
episode is focused around Mannix so
right away you know it's gonna smell
like anyway I'd rather not go on
about this I come you go see it for
yourself so yes as you can see everyone
sock on the ground was not doing right
that is until episode 27 happened and
Knuckles would make his triumphal return
and holy
that's right
Knuckles was back in with him he not
only brought some of the greatest
episodes in soccer neuron history but
also he came back with a big-ass haha
these episodes were so good in fact they
were put together on DVD and they are
now classified as the second official
movie of Sonic Underground well done Nux
well what the yeah it's not going
what's so good then then what happened
well unfortunately it was too late to
save Sonic on the ground
most people who left never came back
as the episodes were reaching the foul
stretch these last episodes would
forever be Mount in history as the foul
season a Sonic Underground unlike these
previous ones these episodes would be
found more story-driven and actually
move the plot forward this would be the
era where we are given the greatest
episode the entire show has ever seen
Bob will be the prisoner bar will be one
of the show's major recurring characters
would make his departure from the show
almost almost as as if we really out
reaching the conclusion I'm not ashamed
to say that crowd no one else you're a
real freedom fighter after such a
beautiful episode you would think that
the final episode would be amazing right
well actually no it's it's actually very
strange I guess I don't really
understand what they were going for
instead of his emotional episode we're
sorry man so you finally reunite with
the mother instead we get this episode
that seems like filler or some and
it's themed around video games I don't
really know what else you say about it
is it's it's a very odd way to go
out with the show I guess is what I'm
trying to say and if you think it
couldn't get any worse just look at the
ending
we will call this advantage Hedgehog
here not here I come
what is he doing game over but Nick yeah
that was it for sure that's supposed to
teach you laugh lessons I don't really
get what's the point here
so basically Sonic hiJacks in airplane
with innocent passengers on board and
flies into one of the most populated
buildings in all of mobile topless just
to teach a lesson
Robotnik's the bad guy what did they do
it's actually severely out of character
for Sonic's personality although to be
fair this isn't the first time Sonic has
shown to have violent tendencies Moby
and I will pinch you
they're bombs from an old mobile army
ammunition dump if we're lucky
but Nickel find one in good condition
and it'll blow up in his face I hope he
likes to travel
cuz he's gonna be scattered all over
Mobius if that bomb goes off I don't
know perhaps they wanted to make the
steward out cut or something but it
really came across as weird I mean
sometimes you don't even know who used
to be rooting for
besides that these episode
in everyone you gotta go watch some
right now I would
here you can see TaMra put together
it holds the five major errors a Sonic
Underground ranging for episode 1 to
present-day
I'll be going through explaining saw
cons popular a few years and where we
are today the first end of course would
be the beginning area this is where I'll
begin after the beginning out we have
the poop these episodes during this time
I'll consider bad that they are put here
let's just say you don't want to be
downwind of that she amor a next
we have viewer viable episodes which
I'll denote as episodes which can argue
to the episodes that single-handedly
halted Sonic undergone his destruction
there are also some people after who
call this the in revival
next we have the golden era this was
where the show was at the peak of its
greatness some people call this the
hidden treasure because it's like power
treasure in some nobody knew he was
so good because by the time I was on TV
most of the haters it all had already
left but the ones who stated holy
lastly we have the legendary thing
called the hero heir or Messiah because
because I am continuing saga and when
the queers have already gave up this is
the most important error as it shows
that Sokka is eternal and has a legacy
of all its own Sonic undergone will be
talked of every now and again through
the years although both instances would
come back to bat Sega in the ass the
first attempt was with the sock on
Archie comics Wasaga I was going to make
a triumphant finish but they gave up on
idea for two reasons one it wouldn't
bring enough money yeah stupid
and the second reason kind of makes
sense they didn't want to on the
saga as director you see he said himself
that he never wanted in ending for the
show and it would ruin the magic yeah
stupid but make sense the other time was
in 2010 in a
videogame believe or not a Sega employee
who was a fan sock Underground put a
picture of Sonya in a video game called
Sega All Star races
unfortunately he stole that picture from
Debbie out and Sega almost got sued for
this Sega has been ignoring sock
around ever since this would eventually
confirmed the rumors that the sock
unknown cast such a Sunni Matic would
not owned by Sega but in fact song
Arne's director dan Hearst well I guess
all we can do now is sit back and wait
for Ben Hearst to decide to tear Sokka
oh oh oh oh yeah I forgot to
mention he's dead six years ago
by the way so you're probably wondering
wait what so what the happens now
well you're gonna have to ask these
but apparently they don't give a
about Sargon so who knows what's
gonna happen from here we can only hope
that Sargon will come back someday but
hey even if it doesn't I will always be
bringing the goods
you